http://www.miuragolf.com/policies/privacy-policy

Privacy policy
(Last updated March 1, 2018)
Miura Golf Inc. (“MIURA”) has established this Privacy Policy to protect and manage your (the customer’s) personal information.
ACCOUNTABILITYMIURA collects, at time of your sign-on to its web site and registration for product purchase, certain “personal information” (information that personally identifies you) such as your name, email address, home or work address, telephone number, and your computer hardware and software (e.g. IP address, operating system, browser type, domain name, URL, access times, and referring web site addresses). MIURA has implemented this Privacy Policy to protect such personal information and to respond to any customer inquiries and complaints. MIURA has designated responsibility for your personal information to its Privacy Officer, who ensures compliance with the principles in this Privacy Policy.
PURPOSES FOR COLLECTING PERSONAL INFORMATIONMIURA collects and uses personal information for the following “Identified Purposes”:(a) to understand its customer needs regarding MIURA’s products;(b) to develop and provide products for its customers;(c) to communicate with its customers, and to inform customers of new products available from MIURA;(d) to allow customers to access limited-entry areas of MIURA’s site;(e) to personalize some of our products for you;(f) to bill accounts and maintain payment records;(g) to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or government request;(h) to protect the products and rights of MIURA; and(i) to identify and resolve technical problems concerning MIURA’s products.
MIURA also uses personal information in an aggregate form (i.e. not individually attributable to you) for its business analysis, operational, marketing and other promotional purposes. If we hire other companies to provide some products or services on our behalf, then we will only provide those companies the personal information they need to carry out the Identified Purposes.
CONSENT FOR COLLECTION, USE OR DISCLOSUREUse of the MIURA web site and registration for MIURA products will constitute the customer’s consent for MIURA to collect, use and disclose personal information under this Privacy Policy for the Identified Purposes. MIURA will normally seek a customer’s additional consent for any new uses and disclosures of the customer’s personal information, either at the same time it collects the personal information or after it has been collected but before it is used or disclosed for a new purpose. In certain circumstances however, MIURA will not be required to inform and obtain the consent of the customer, such as investigation of a breach of an agreement, contravention of laws, an emergency where the life, health or security of an individual is threatened, or the collection of a debt. A customer may withdraw by prior written notice the consent for MIURA’s collection, use and disclosure of the customer’s personal information, at any time, provided that MIURA may as a result terminate its sale of products or limit access to its web site.
LIMITING THE COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATIONMIURA limits its collection of personal information to only that information which is necessary for the Identified Purposes. MIURA does not knowingly collect personal information from children. When you visit the MIURA web site, a cookie may be placed on your computer or the cookie may be read if you have visited the MIURA site previously. MIURA uses cookies to allow MIURA to better serve you by determining what products and information you are interested in. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the MIURA web site, you may not be able to view all the text on the screens, or to experience a personalised visit, or to subscribe to certain product offerings on the MIURA site.
DISCLOSURE, PROCESSING AND RETENTIONMIURA does not sell, rent or disclose your personal information to anyone else except, when the Identified Purposes require MIURA to disclose the personal information to:(a) an agent of the customer;(b) agents of MIURA acting on its behalf for the Identified Purposes;(c) a public authority, to avoid or minimize danger to life or property and(b) a third party to which disclosure is required by any law, regulation, legal process or government request.
Your information may be stored and processed in Canada, the United States, or in any other country in which MIURA or its agents maintain facilities. By using this web site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. After your account becomes inactive, MIURA will keep your personal information only for those purposes which are established by law, and for archival record purposes.
ACCURACY OF PERSONAL INFORMATIONMIURA will use reasonable efforts to keep customer personal information accurate for the Identified Purposes. Customers are responsible for informing MIURA about changes to their personal information. MIURA will update personal information when necessary to keep it accurate or else provide to its customers the facilities to make such updates.
SECURITY SAFEGUARDSMIURA uses reasonable efforts to protect your personal information against loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, misuse or modification, through security safeguards that depend on the level of sensitivity of the information. MIURA will disclose personal information to third parties subject to agreements which contain confidentiality provisions and restrictions on use which are consistent with this Privacy Policy.
OPENNESS OF POLICYThis Privacy Policy, and all updates to the Privacy Policy made from time to time, are published and made available to MIURA’s customers on its web site www.miuragolf.com. It is the customer’s obligation to periodically check the MIURA web site for Privacy Policy updates.
ACCESS TO PERSONAL INFORMATIONMIURA will normally afford you a reasonable opportunity to review the personal information in your file upon request through the MIURA web site or to the Privacy Officer made by you after providing sufficient identification. If MIURA is not able to provide access to some aspect of a customer’s personal information, it will provide reasons for denying access such as; that by doing so would likely reveal personal information about a third party, or that it is attorney–client privileged communications, or that the information relates to a breach of an agreement or a contravention of law, or that its disclosure could reasonably be expected to threaten the life or security of another individual. Customers have the right to request that inaccurate or incomplete information be amended as appropriate, and MIURA will promptly correct such personal information or provide the means for you to do so directly.
POLICY IMPROVEMENTS AND COMPLIANCEMIURA wants to ensure that its Privacy Policy meets its customers’ needs. If you feel that the Privacy Policy needs improvement, or believe that MIURA is not following its Privacy Policy, please contact the Privacy Officer at the address shown in this web site. MIURA will investigate your suggestions and complaints concerning its Privacy Policy. If a complaint is found to be justified, MIURA will take appropriate measures to resolve the complaint including, if necessary, amending its policies and procedures. Each customer will be informed of the outcome of the investigation regarding the customer’s complaint. In some jurisdictions a customer may have a legal right to appeal the decision or otherwise have it reviewed.
Quick Links
Contact us
FAQ
Order Requests
Trade-In Program
Financing
Miura Blog
Warranty
Join our mailing list and stay updated with everything Miura
Refund Policy
Terms of Service
Privacy Policy
Copyright © 2020 Miura Golf. All rights reserved.
